Guide to the Travel brochure and map collection, [19--].
Travel brochure and map collection, [19--]
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Travel brochure and map collection, [19--].
6591
6.0 cubic ft.
Maps/Charts, Printed Materials, Publications
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
The collection contains travel guides, road maps, brochures, leaflets, post cards, and souvenir publications relating to various states of the United States and foreign countries all around the world.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
The collection contains travel guides, road maps, brochures, leaflets, post cards, and souvenir publications relating to various states of the United States and foreign countries all around the world.
SUBJECTS
Subjects:
Travel.; Tourism.
Form and Genre Terms:
Travel guidebooks.; Picture postcards.; Pamphlets.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Description: City/ Region, State
  - Travel Brochure: Mobile, Alabama (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Advertising leaflet: Daphne, Alabama (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Natchez Trace Parkway map: States, Alabama, Mississippi, Tennessee (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Exxon maps (2): States, Alabama, Georgia (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Enco map: States, Alabama, Georgia (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Lodging: Petersburg, Alaska (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - State Guide: Entire, Alaska (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Exxon Map: Entire, Arizona (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Mobil Map: Phoenix, Arizona (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Trip Guide: Grand Canyon, Arizona (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Landscape and Geology: Grand Canyon, Arizona (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Courthouse park: Tombstone, Arizona (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - S. Rim region guide: Grand Canyon, Arizona (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Region Guide: Tuzigoot, Arizona (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Rincon Mountain guide: Saguaro Nat. Monument, Arizona (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - U. S. Dept. of Interior leaflet: Saguaro Nat. Monument, Arizona (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Desert museum: Tucson, Arizona (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Arizona Winter: Santa Fe (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - By the Way: Santa Fe (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Grand Canyon Outings: Santa Fe (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Indian-detour: Santa Fe (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Travel guide: Grand Canyon, Arizona (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Park Guide: Grand Canyon, Arizona (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - El Tovar Grand Canyon, Arizona (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Travel guide: Summer trips, Grand Canyon, Arizona (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Leaflet: Tuzigoot National Monument (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Hot Springs Guide: Hot Springs, Arkansas (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Map: Hot Springs, Arkansas (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Territorial restoration: Little Rock, Arkansas (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - American Automobile Association map: Arkansas, Louisiana, Mississippi, Arkansas (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - AAA map: Arkansas, Oklahoma, Arkansas (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Trailways: South, Southwest and New England, Bus time tables (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - State Park Guide: Entire, California (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Map: Northwest, California (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Map: Inyo-Sierra, California (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Map: Entire, California (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Map: Monterey, California (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Map: Santa Cruz, California (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Map: Los Angeles Freeway, California (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Map: Monterey/ San Benito, California (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Wine Country Tour Map, California (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Park guide: Bale Grist Mill, California (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Bothe Guide: Napa Valley, California (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Park Guide: Clear Lake, California (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Park Guide: Cuyamanca Rancho, California (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Park History: Death Valley, California (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Map: Death Valley/ Grand Canyon, California (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - History: Myrtlewood, California (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Redwood park guide: Humbolt, California (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Garden Guide: Huntington Desert, California (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Park Guide: Jedediah Smith Redwood, California (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Tree Monument: Joshua Tree, California (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Park Map: Joshua Tree, California (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Tree Monument: Joshua Tree, California (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Guide: Palm Oases/Joshua Tree Monument, California (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Motoring Guide: Joshua Tree, California (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Park Guide: Muir Woods, California (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Travel Guide: Oakland, California (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Park Guide: Point lobos, California (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Guide: Redwood Natl. Park, California (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Park Guide: Richardson Grove, California (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Recreation guide: Salton Sea, California (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - State Park guide: Patrick Point, California (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Map: Pebble Beach, California (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Tour Map: San Francisco, California (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Golden Gate: San Francisco, California (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - San Jacinto Mill: San Jacinto, California (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Map: Sequoia Natl. Park, California (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Map and Guide: Sequoia Natl. Park, California (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Park History: Sequoia Natl. Park, California (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Weaverville Joss House: Sacramento, California (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Guide: Yosemite, California (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Guide: Yosemite, California (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Activity Guide: Yosemite, California (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Guide: Yosemite, California (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Trail Guide: Yosemite, California (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Map: Yosemite, California (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Map: Yosemite, California (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Park Guide: Yosemite, California (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Doan's Directory of the United States/Wonders of America/Gateway to the Yosemite Valley California (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Freeway System: Los Angeles, California (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Metropolitan region: Los Angeles, California (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Samoa Cookhouse: Eureka, California (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Fullerton Hacienda: Fullerton, California (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Travel service: San Francisco, California (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Highway Guide: Pacific Coast, California (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Tour: San Diego, California (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Rand McNally Map: San Diego, California (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Queen Mary Tour: Long Beach, California (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Exxon Map: Entire, California (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Exxon maps (2): States, California, Nevada (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Esso map: States, Central and Western United States (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - AAA nap: States and southern areas of Canadian central provinces, Central States and Provinces (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - City Guide: Denver, Colorado (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Natl. Park: Rocky Mountain, Colorado (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Park Map: Rocky Mountain, Colorado (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Park Guide: Rocky Mountain, Colorado (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Park Guide: Rocky Mountain, Colorado (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Rail Guide: Rocky Mountain, Colorado (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Park Guide: Rocky Mountain, Colorado (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Natl. Park Guide: Mesa Verde, Colorado (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Rail Museum: Denver, Colorado (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - MobilTravel Map: Denver/Colorado Spring/ Pueblo, Colorado (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - A Train Trip to Fremont County, Colorado (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Esso map: New York harbor to Savannah, Cruising guide (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Texaco waterways service maps (2): Great Lakes and adjoining waterways, Cruising guide (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Standard Oil map: States, Delaware, Maryland, Virginia, West Virginia (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Esso map(2 editions): States, Delaware, Maryland, Virginia, West Virginia (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Exxon map: States, Delaware, Maryland, Virginia, West Virginia (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Socony-Vacuum Oil Company map: States, Delaware, New Jersey, and adjoining territory (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Esso map: Minnesota to East Coast, Eastern U. S. (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Exxon map: Minnesota to East Coast, Eastern U.S. (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - State Info: Entire, Florida (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Map: West Coast, Florida (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Exxon Map: Miami, Florida (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Map: Central Area, Florida (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Enco Map: Entire, Florida (2 c.) (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Visitor's Guide: St. Augustine, Florida (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Tour Guide: Kennedy Space center, Florida (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Epcot Guides: Orlando, Florida (3 different) (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Atlantic Map: Miami, Florida (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Nasa Guide: Space Center, Florida (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Exxon Map: Entire, Florida (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Enco Map: Entire, Florida (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Map: Greater Deland, Florida (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Enco Map: Jacksonville, Florida (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Texaco Map: Entire, Florida (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Gulf Info Map: Entire, Florida (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Realtor Map: Naples, Florida (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - AAA Map: Miami/ Beach/ Fort Lauderdale, Florida (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - AAA map: Pinellas, Florida (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Circus Guide: Sarasota, Florida (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Collier museum: Naples, Florida (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Natl. Park guide: Everglades, Florida (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Alligator Guide: Everglades, Florida (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Map: Gulf Islands, Florida (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Map: Sanibel, Florida (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Tourist Guide: Winter Park, Florida (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Natl. Monument Guide: Castillo de San Marcos, Florida (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Shell Map: Tampa St. Petersburg, Florida (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Gulf Tourguide Map (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Walt Disney World, Epcot Center: maps (3 c.) (Box 1, Folder 22A)
  - U.S. 287 Highway Association: U. S. 287, Florida to Alaska (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Texaco Map: Entire, Georgia (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - American Map: Entire, Georgia (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Greenhouse Layout: Callaway, Georgia (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Travel Brochure: Brunswick, Georgia (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Visitors Guide: Jekyll Island, Georgia (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Map: Milledgey, Georgia (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Standard Oil Map: Entire, Georgia (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Pebble Hill: Thomasville, Georgia (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Pebble Hill map: Thomasville, Georgia (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - The Planters rest.: Marietta, Georgia (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Map: Cobb, Georgia (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Park sites: Entire, Georgia (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Historic events: Savannah, Georgia (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Trolley tours: Savannah, Georgia (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Highway Map: Entire, Georgia (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Tybee Island: Savannah, Georgia (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Map: Atlanta, Georgia (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Map: Stone Mountain, Georgia (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Texaco Map: Entire, Hawaii (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Historical guide: Lahaina, Hawaii (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Park Guide: Nez Perce, Idaho (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Enco map: States, Idaho, Montana, Wyoming (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Exxon map: States, Idaho, Montana, Wyoming (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Exxon Map: Entire, Illinois (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - AAA Map: Entire, Illinois (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Standard Map: Chicago, Illinois (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Mobil Map: Chicago, Illinois (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Shell Map: Chicago, Illinois (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Seeing Chicago Right/free map and guide to: Chicago, Illinois (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Park Guide: New Salem, Illinois (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Lincoln History: Ohio River, Illinois (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Park Guide: New Salem, Illinois (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Lincoln Statues: Fort Wayne, Illinois (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Lodging: Chicago, Illinois (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - AAA map: Arizona, New Mexico, Utah, Colorado, Indian country (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - AAA Road Map: Entire, Indiana (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Ninth Annual Report of Board of Park Commissioners, 1913: Fort Wayne, Indiana (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Rand McNally: Continental U.S., Interstate U.S. (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Eisenhower Library: Abilene, Kansas (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Pony Express Station: Hanover, Kansas (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - AAA Map: Cincinnati, Kentucky (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Lincoln Pilgrimage: Detroit Area council, Kentucky (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Geology Guide: Mammoth Cave, Kentucky (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Walking Tour: Paducah, Kentucky (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Map and Guide: Cumberland Gap, Kentucky (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Map: Mammoth Cave, Kentucky (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Highway Map: Entire, Louisiana (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Highway Map: Entire, Louisiana (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Railroad Map: Entire, Louisiana (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Brochure: Sulphur, Louisiana (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Street Map: New Orleans, Louisiana (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Basilica on Jackson square: New Orleans, Louisiana (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - AAA map: States, Louisiana, Mississippi (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - State Facts: Entire, Maine (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Route Mao: Entire, Maine (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Hunting Fishing Guide: Entire, Maine (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Street Map: Baltimore, Maryland (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Exxon Map: Baltimore, Maryland (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Civil War sites: Entire, Maryland (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Atlantic Map: Baltimore, Maryland (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Visitor's guide: Frederick County, Maryland (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Mountain Thunder RR: Western, Maryland (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - AAA map: Annapolis & southern Anne Arundel County, Maryland (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Fort Washington, Maryland (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Tourists' Guide: Entire, Massachusetts (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Historic Sites: Boston, Massachusetts (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Sight Seeing Colonial Tours: Boston, Massachusetts (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Shell Map: Boston, Massachusetts (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Socony Map: Boston, Massachusetts (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Rand McNally Guide: Boston, Massachusetts (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Views: Boston, Massachusetts (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Faneuil Hall: Boston, Massachusetts (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Public Library: Boston, Massachusetts (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - 2nd Bunker Hill Oration: Bunker Hill, Massachusetts (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Guide: Fascinating TYrips to Historic Spots in and about Boston, Massachusetts (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Guide: Isabella Stewart Gardner Museum, Boston, Massachusetts (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Map, Massachusetts Turnpike (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Standard Map: Detroit, Michigan (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Tourist Council: Ironwood, Michigan (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Hiawatha association: Great Lakes, Michigan (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Skiing: Ironwood, Michigan (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Car Ferry: Lake Michigan, Michigan (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Chessie Cruise: Lake Michigan, Michigan (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - C&O/B&O Ferry: Lake Michigan, Michigan (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Museum Guides: Entire, Michigan (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Esso map: Maryland to South Carolina, Middle Atlantic States (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Post Card: Entire, Minnesota (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Standard Map: Entire, Minnesota (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Texaco Map: Minneapolis/ St. Paul, Minnesota (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Tour Guide: Vicksburg, Mississippi (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Tours: Entire, Mississippi (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Casino Magic: Biloxi, Mississippi (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Rest.: Biloxi, Mississippi (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Antique Shops: Gulf Port, Mississippi (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Travel Brochure: Tupelo, Mississippi (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Natl. Military Park: Vicksburg, Mississippi (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Prairie Museum: Columbia, Missouri (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Truman Library: Independence, Missouri (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Museum + Pony Express: St. Joseph, Missouri (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Pony Express postcard: St. Joseph, Missouri (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Map: St. Joseph, Missouri (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Site guide + History: Jefferson Natl. Expansion Memorial, Missouri (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Standard Map: Kansas City, Missouri (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Postcards: Greetings from Kansas City, Missouri (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Visitors Guide: bicentennial, St. Louis, Missouri (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Official Bicentennial Calendar: Today and Tomorrow in St. Louis, Missouri (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Hor to enjoy your stay in St. Louis, Missouri (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Walking Tour: Downtown St. Louis, Missouri (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Map: Saint Louis and surrounding areas, Missouri (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Booklet with map: Missouri Holiday, entire state, Missouri (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Enco History: Entire, Montana (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Map: Entire, Montana (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Indian Museum: Browning, Montana (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Ft. Peck Dam and Lake: Ft. Peck, Montana (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Ft. Peck Lake: Ft. Peck, Montana (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Recreation Area: Hungry Horse Reservoir, Montana (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Natl. Bison Range: Moiese, Montana (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - U. S. Dept of Interior: American Buffalo, Montana (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Travel Brochure: Polson, Montana (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Historical site: St. Ignatius Mission, Montana (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Street Map: Great Falls, Montana (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Trail Map: Glacier Natl Park, Montana (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Enco Map: Billings, Montana (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Enco Map: Billings, Montana (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Hanging Valley: Glacier Natl Park, Montana (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Two Medicine: Glacier Natl Park, Montana (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Map + Fishing: Glacier Natl Park, Montana (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Geological Survey: Glacier Natl Park, Montana (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Waterton Lakes: Glacier Natl Park, Montana (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Plantlife: Glacier Natl Park, Montana (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Tour Guide: Glacier Natl Park, Montana (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - St. Mary Lodge: Glacier Natl Park, Montana (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Natl. Park Guide: Glacier Natl Park, Montana (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Map: Glacier Natl Park, Montana (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Brochure: Glacier Natl Park, Montana (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Tourist Guide: Glacier Natl Park, Montana (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Waterton Valley maps (2): Glacier Natl Park, Montana (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Map: Glacier Natl Park, Montana (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Map: Glacier Natl Park, Montana (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Waterton Lake: Glacier Natl Park, Montana (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - U.S. Dept of Agriculture Forest Service: Continental U.S., National Forest Vacations (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - U. S. Dept of Interior: Continental U.S., National Monuments (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - U.S Gov't Printing Office (2): Continental U.S., Hawaii, & Alaska, Glimpses of Our National Parks (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - U. S. Dept. of the Interior: All parts of U.S., National Park System (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Standard map: Omaha, Council Bluffs, Nebraska (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Feather and Yuba Rivers: Hoover Dam, Nevada (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Map + Guide: Hoover Dam, Nevada (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - History + Recreation: Hoover Dam, Nevada (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - AAA map: New England & Southern Eastern Canada, New England (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Socony Vacuum Oil Company map (2): New England & Southern Eastern Canada, New England (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - New England Hotel Association 1932 eclipse edition & clipping: New England & Southern Eastern Canada, New England Tours (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Mt. Washington Summit Road Co.: Mount Washington, New Hampshire (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Exxon Map: Entire, New Jersey (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Road Map: Entire, New Jersey (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Standard Map: Entire, New Jersey (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Esso Map: Entire, New Jersey (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Esso Map: Entire, New Jersey (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Ferry: Cape May-Lewes, New Jersey (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Map: Essex, New Jersey (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Atlantic Map: Newark, New Jersey (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Map: Newark, New Jersey (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Map: Somerville, New Jersey (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Map: Summmit, New Jersey (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Turnpike Guide: Entire, New Jersey (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Skiing: Taos, New Mexico (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Hot Springs: Truth Or Consequences, New Mexico (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Lodging: Death Valley, New Mexico (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Natl. Park Guide: Carlsbad Caverns, New Mexico (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Attraction Guide: Various, New Mexico (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Socony Standard Map: Entire, New York (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Soconyland Standard Map: Entire, New York (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Soconyland Standard Map: Entire, New York (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Soconyland Standard Map: Entire, New York (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Soconyland Standard Map: Entire, New York (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Soconyland Standard Map: Entire, New York (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Mobilgas Map: Entire, New York (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Texaco Map: Entire, New York (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Map Corp. Map: Buffalo, New York (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - World's Fair Edition Map: Entire, New York (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Map: Entire, New York (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Texaco Map: Entire, New York (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Map: Entire, New York (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Socony Standard Map: Entire, New York (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Boughton Map: Entire, New York (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Road + Land Map: Dutchess, New York (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Esso Map: Westchester + Putnam, New York (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Rand McNally Pocket maps: Entire, New York (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Calso Map: Entire, New York (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Socony Map: Entire, New York (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Esso Pictorial Guide: Entire, New York (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Flashmaps Guide: Entire, New York (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Lodging guide: Niagara, New York (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Recreation map: Entire, New York (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - AAA Map: New York (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Historic Erie County, New York (2) (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Mobil Map: Rochester/ Buffalo/ Niagara, New York (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Esso Map: Rockland/Westchester, New York (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - I Love New York Tourism Map: Entire, New York (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Esso travel map: Entire, New York (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Mobil Map: Greater New York (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Marine Midland Map: Entire, New York (2 editions) (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Seaway Power projects: Various, New York (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - State info: Entire, New York (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Outdoor Recreation Map: Albany, New York (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Mobil Travel Map: Greater NY, New York (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - I LOVE NY Tourist Map: Entire, New York (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Map: Entire, New York (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Mobil Travel Map: entire New York (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - State University Maps: Buffalo, New York (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Champion Map: Albany/ Schenectady/ Troy, New York (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Esso Map: New York with Sight Seeing Guide (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Photocopied Map: Upstate New York (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Saranac Lake: Adirondacks, New York (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Map of Interests: Adirondacks, New York (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Campsites: Adirondacks, New York (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Lake Champlain Bridge: Adirondacks, New York (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Forest Reserve: Adirondacks, New York (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Loj Club: Adirondacks, New York (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Lake George: Adirondacks, New York (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Meet the Town: Saranac Lake, New York (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Trudeau Sanatorium, Saranac Lake, New York (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Glens Falls, New York (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Lake Champlain Bridge/Rouses Point Bridge, Crown Point, New York (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Whiteface Mountain: New York State, New York (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Whiteface Mt.: New York State, New York (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Trail Map: Lake Placid, New York (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Trail Guide: Lake Placid, New York (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Shore Owners Assc.: Lake Placid, New York (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Lake Placid Club: Lake Placid, New York (Box 2, Folder 13)